iyogi.com 2014-06-28

# Privacy: iYogi

This privacy policy explains how iYogi Inc ("iYogi") collects, uses and discloses personal and other information iYogi receives in connection with the user support services we provide to user (the "Services") in accordance with the Terms of Use (<http://www.iyogi.net/terms.html>). When you submit information through our website, email, chat session, provide it to our technicians or, use the Services, you(the "user") agree to our use of this information consistent with this privacy policy.

###### HOW IYOGI COLLECTS INFORMATION

We provide user support services to consumers using web-based tools and software as well as through telephone support of our users. These tools may include software that enables us to remotely access and control a user’s computer with their permission. We require certain information and permissions from you to provide the Services.

Some information we collect may be provided by the user directly such as when requested by a form or on the phone by a technician. Other technical information might be collected or accessed by or through our diagnostic and related tools as our computers work with yours to provide the Services.

###### TYPES OF INFORMATION IYOGI COLLECTS

Information You Provide

###### PERSONAL INFORMATION:

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you ("personal information") or allows us to contact you. In order to use the Services, the user must first typically register or provide certain identifying information. For online registration, we ask you to provide contact details (such as First and Last name, E-mail address, Postal address, Personal identifier etc.). iYogi uses this information to contact you regarding the product and/or services you have requested. This includes re-registration/renewal notifications, special offers, and surveys on improving our Services.

###### PAYMENT INFORMATION:

If you register for the Services, iYogi may collect credit card information, and other payment information. Like many companies, iYogi may use third party payment processing, payment gateways transactions to process and verify credit cards on our behalf. iYogi uses payment information to complete your transactions.

_Computer and System Information_

###### SUBSCRIBER( USER) COMPUTER INFORMATION:

We may also ask for information related to your (user) computer to provide the Service. As examples, this information may include:

  * information about the date of purchase of your computer,
  * type of computer
  * identification number of your computer
  * make and model of your computer and/or any computer hardware,
  * software installed or peripherals attached to it,
  * condition of the computer,
  * system and registry data about software installations and hardware configurations, and 

error tracking files.

Generally, this information is required to provide personalized technical support to you, and to help us update our support tools and enhance our supported products lists.

###### REMOTE ACCESS:

While requesting support you may request for the problem to be resolved by enabling iYogi technicians to have access to and take control of your computer. iYogi uses software tools which enable you to grant control of your computer to an iYogi technician remotely over the Internet. This allows the iYogi technician to diagnose or correct problems without ever coming to the location of your computer.

iYogi does not use the Remote Access software to access and control your computer without your consent and we request that you remain present when our technicians are doing so.

iYogi technicians are trained in the use of this software and we take steps to limit access to confidential or sensitive information stored on user computer or network, avoid deliberate destruction of information on user computers or networks, and help avoid system problems. iYogi maintains specific internal policy and technical controls to limit how and whether our remote access tools may be used to assist you.

###### DIAGNOSTIC TOOL:

iYogi uses some online diagnostic tolls that may collect a wide variety of useful information about the state of a computer system and your applications. This information is communicated to Yogi using security technologies over the Internet. iYogi analyzes this information to help diagnose and solve end-user problems. The iYogi diagnostic application is not designed to collect sensitive information including information such websites visited, e-mail messages, e-mail addresses sent to, passwords, profiles, etc.

Use of the Remote Access and Diagnostic applications may be subject to the terms and conditions of the respective software license agreements.

###### LIVE HELP SESSION RECORDS:

iYogi reserves the right to monitor and record on-line and off-line sessions between users and iYogi technicians for quality control and service-related purposes. Some uses of this type of information include improving the Service, building a support knowledge base and conducting internal market research. We do not correlate session record data used for these purposes with personal information.

###### COOKIES:

We may use cookies and similar technologies to provide you with more personal service on our website and as you interact with iYogi. Cookies are small pieces of information stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive or on your device. Cookies help us keep track of the preferences you specify. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that if you prefer not to store the information for future use. Each browser is different, so please check the help menu of your browser.

###### LOG FILES:

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the website, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

###### SUPPLEMENTATION OF INFORMATION

In order to protect iYogi from fraud and otherwise ensure the integrity of our services and manage risk we may supplement personal information we collect with information we may get from others. For example, in connection with determining creditworthiness, we may use your name and other related information to request a credit report as permitted by law.

###### SHARING AND INFORMATION DISCLOSURE

We may share aggregated and de-identified information with our partners. This sharing is usually not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person, unless specifically required to allow use of specific widgets within the Services.

We may also share, disclose, or transfer your personal information as follows:

  * To iYogi affiliates and subsidiaries to support business operations and sales, marketing, and customer support processes;
  * To third party service providers and suppliers acting on our behalf to provide products or services to you; and
  * To other third parties for purposes you have allowed.

Additionally, we may also disclose your personal information as we determine reasonably necessary to (a) comply with applicable law, regulations, legal processes, or enforceable governmental requests, (b) respond as necessary to actual or potential lawsuits, or (c) protect the rights and property of iYogi or others.

We reserve the right to retain, use, and disclose aggregate or anonymous information developed from personal information at any time.

If we merge with, or are acquired by another company, or sell all or substantially all of our relevant assets, or file for bankruptcy, we may disclose and transfer personal information with the company or asset. We will seek appropriate protection for personal information disclosed or transferred in such transactions consistent with applicable law.

###### INTERNATIONAL USERS

Because iYogi operates globally, we make information we gather available to our worldwide business units. If you are in the European Economic Area, please note that the personal information you provide will be transferred outside the European Economic Area for use by iYogi and its affiliates and subsidiaries for any of the purposes described in this privacy policy. By using the the iYogi website, using the Services, or otherwise providing us with your personal information, you consent to the transfer and processing of your personal information.

###### SECURITY

We use a variety of security technologies, as well as administrative, managerial, and physical safeguards, to help protect personal information and other data we receive from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. No data transmissions, or even the physical transfer of information, can be guaranteed to be completely secure. We cannot fully eliminate all security risks associated with personal information and technical mistakes are possible. Therefore, we do not ensure or warrant the security of any data or information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

###### SURVEYS

From time-to-time we may request information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and users have a choice whether or not to participate. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of Services.

###### CONTESTS

iYogi may offer contests, sweepstakes or other promotions. These promotions will be governed by applicable rules. Personal information collected through such promotions will be used as described at the time of collection.

###### CHILDREN

Our Services are not intended for use by anyone under the age of 13. Consistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, we do not collect or maintain information at our website from or sell products to those we actually know are under the age of 13.

###### CORRECTION/UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION

If a user's personal information changes (such as user zip code), or if a user no longer desires to use the Service. User may correct, update or remove user personal information provided to us through our website.

###### NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

We reserve the right to change our privacy policy. Please check our website periodically for changes so that you are aware of our latest privacy practices. For changes that are materially less restrictive or protective of your personal information than the privacy policy in place at the time of collection, we will notify before implementing any such change.

###### QUESTIONS

If you have any questions about our privacy policy you may email questions or inquiries to [feedback@iyogi.net](mailto://feedback@iyogi.net) or [cpo@iyogi.com](mailto://cpo@iyogi.com)
